Coming out, coming out!
Please tell me something
Is it true that butane gas exploded?
Suddenly an investigation
What's the reason for the rush?
Please tell me!
I...
My hair was burnt.
The dining table fell over
This makes sense, right?
Butane gas exploded
The entire ATM machine was blown away?
This is not a joke
Ah, if it has that much firepower
Why is North Korea making missiles?
Do you shoot this way and that way?
It's better to have ours delivered
So I am
So, when this thing explodes
I was in front of you, uh
But then I was like this
I quickly fell down and it was like this.
Oh, if it weren't for that
I might have gone to the other world
Look, someone died at dawn.
At that location the next morning
What a new machine!
Come in and sit down, okay?
No, what
Are you in a hurry to withdraw money like that? uh?
As soon as you put away the invoice?
This is not it
ATM machine explodes
A few days later, in Giyun City,
one more time
An explosion occurred
I can see behind me now
At the village bus terminal
the bus explodes
This is an incident in which two citizens died.
But the government
Why hasn't there been any announcement yet?
Why don't we do it?
It just exploded.
Well, it catches fire and smoke comes out.
Without anything like that
Just crap
Uh, back then...
- Huh? It's mom
- It's mom, mom.
- Quiet, quiet
- Mom
It comes out scary well.
Right?
At the last stop of the village bus
There was car number 1
Are you sure you saw it?
But how do you know about car number 1?
Well, if you look at Letona, you will get the answer.
Anyway
It's so clogged there
I just crawled in front of it
No, but police and firefighters
Have a gatekeeper
Soldiers are cleaning up the scene
Tell me to protect my country
They sent the army
Well, clean up with water.
I didn't send it.
If you are going to provide public support,
Provide support to save people
Not butane gas
suspected to be a bomb
with experts
eyewitness statements
Soldiers deployed to the scene of the accident
Above all, the incident
I want to finish it urgently
Until the government moves
This is full of suspicion
Kiyun City serial explosion accident
What is the truth?
What is the government hiding?
Did you see the video?
Who posted this?
You bastard
Don't let things like this come up, Mr.
It's done
until we find out
Don’t let anyone approach Kiyun City.
88th Transportation Brigade
You're saying you didn't leave?
Then what about Unit 900 or Logistics Support Group?
no
Why is there talk about the 5th generation?
There is a witness who saw a military vehicle.
There are no troops dispatched
Does that make sense!
keep looking
These are playing around
Isn’t that something they really don’t know?
Then it's more of a problem
The four gathered together
Find out what they said
Kiyun City explodes
I think there's a connection.
yes
It's confidential
I'll keep that in mind
Um...
Okay, now
Then, let's organize it
Is it a spy or the National Intelligence Service?
I went to check
I saw a doll there too
So this computer was also found?
Yes
With the man who died at the ATM
The man who came out of the mall was one of the gang.
That village bus explosion is also related.
- Right?
- Yes, that's right.
This is the rabbit doll
It's
So this is the reporter
You're really good at organizing things, huh.
But the mercenary with that weapon
How did you subdue it?
Uh...
I'm making a fist.
- Hey!
I also came from HID
You know, that unit? uh?
You know that movie, uh
‘Except for the gold teeth’
‘I’ll chew it all up and eat it for you’
wing
Hey
Oh, I'm good at running.
Yes, I mean
So we just fight
Yeah, he runs away
That's right, hey!
But
Report all this to me
What is the reason?
I am
Why did Myung-oh die?
I want to know the truth
Ah, people in the neighborhood are dying.
You don't have to do anything
Me too
For no reason I
Bring this computer, huh?
I wonder if something like this happened
Why is it your fault, nigga
Hey, this is off...
This doesn't turn on
So
You need to clone the original computer
Forensically extracting information
Let's get some evidence?
And the computer
Because my location is being tracked
I intentionally gave away the location
Let’s get a corporation?
Then first
From that computer CMOS battery
I have to catch it
Hey, that's
I'll do it, uh
Okay
Everyone knows that and disperses!
Hey, wait a minute
What are you going to do?
I have to go to work!
I'm an office worker!
Okay, dismissed.
Hey, but really...
Hey, look at the car.
Hey, you are young.
Like this, huh?
No, why are they
Does it all come from there?
Except me
Wow, with this computer
It'll take a million years
"C4 explosion"
The snack bag is made of polypropylene.
It's made by evaporating aluminum.
electricity, magnetic field
You can even block communication.
Because it's in such a dangerous place.
My mom doesn't let me eat cookies.
Sweets are delicious, but
It's dangerous
It has nothing to do with that at all...
Of course it doesn't matter
Just kidding
Hey, Police Officer Park!
People die here, people
- Why, why, uh, where!
- People die!
Where, where, where!
me
I think I'm going to fall and die
Wow, really, it's a surprise, really!
Hey, just buy me a cup of coffee
Hey
No, it's a hot and spicy coffee shop.
Do you really need to come to the police box and get coffee?
Hey, near the coffee shop
There is no coffee vending machine here.
I like this the best
Ah, hey, it’s nothing else.
who lived in that villa
There are foreigners, huh?
I was in room 203
I brought something with me
Ah, but it's a bit scary.
And it looks a little dangerous, so
To leave it to the police
no
Why did you do that...
Hey, I
Did you know that, huh?
- Please
- Uh
I'm embroidering, huh?
Please take into account the circumstances
"Location: Changni-dong, Giyun City"
“No signal”
To the company
I think I should leave it to you.
I can do it, but I don't have the equipment.
How much is it?
Data extraction, memory analysis
Even reverse engineering
You need money to do it...
Oh, so how much is it all?
2,000?
2,000 won?
Hey, really 20 million won?
uh?
Is this it?
yes
Man, this is too much
Isn't this too expensive?
Wait a minute
Then divide by five
No, if we divide it between the four of us, excluding the students.
4 5 20
500?
Hey, do it in installments, do it in installments
Uh, in installments.
Okay, make it 120 months.
yes
First of all, another way
I'll have to look into it.
I bought it
- Did you buy it?
- uh?
What kind of money does a student earn?
By how many months?
It's a lump sum payment.
Umkaro
- Wow, rich, rich.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- With mom’s permission...
- He's rich.
Mom, are you okay?
Anyway, the equipment is coming.
Until the equipment arrives
Let me do some research.
- Yes, I will prepare a follow-up report.
- Uh
computer signal
Because it was cut off at the police box
They'll come there
Hey, then we
Let's go undercover at the police box, okay?
They come at night after work.
Not tomorrow night
Because we have houses
Oh, really?
Hey, then if we all go
Who protects it?
Where are you going?
They said they were having a housewarming party
all of us
Shouldn’t I go?
Uh... I'm fine.
I have to attend, Doyeon is the instructor.
Are you all crazy?
Did you call the company people?
From the beginning
I wasn't going to go
Fish oil, indeed
Baby, then
from the beginning
Don't say 'our housewarming'
Well, people from the company, people from the neighborhood.
Discrimination? uh?
Oh, then who does the hiding?
That's cloud CCTV.
You can record it
on memory card
Without wifi
Data charges are high
Hey, how much is that?
battery, memory
I ordered the biggest one
Hey
Hey, hey, what's wrong?
You, you next part...
Next time it happens again
Can't you see us, huh?
- Brother, Jeonghwan brother
- Jeonghwan hyung
- Yeah, hey, yeah.
- It's my brother, bro.
Hey, thank you, thank you, uh
Wow
Oh, really!
A
Hey, I thought you were a ghost.
Are you installing CCTV on your car now?
uh?
Oh, this?
This is a custom black box.
So this is
It's sent to the cloud, huh?
Someone scratched my car
Then text me
It just flies right in, this
Ha! The text is stupid
Yonghee
The phone is off now
you are here now
I'm doing this shit
You think I don’t know, huh?
Are you guys
Except old me
Are you hanging out with young guys now?
uh? Did you drink and drink liquor?
Wow
If my brother isn't at the drinking party,
What fun is there, huh?
Oh, and
Me and my brother
Only one year difference, one year difference
I do it tomorrow too
Eat well and live well with CCTV, tumblr
Eh?
Goodbye, bro.
uh
I'll contact you later
Don't sulk!
What should I buy?
Four bottles of soju, four bottles of beer
four bottles of soju
- Four bottles of beer
- One soju
two
Ssamjang
Ssamjang!
I'm going to make braised ribs, so please give me plenty.
Braised ribs
Then
Can I give you two packs of these?
yes
Please give me two packs of pork belly too.
Pork belly?
Dad, where did you go?
- Did you buy everything?
- Yes
- Uh, let's go now.
Now
It's here
- thank you
- Go ahead, okay.
- Goodbye.
-Have a good housewarming
- Hello, sweetie.
- Yes
- Hello, yes.
- Kang is your younger brother?
- Hello, Doyeon, hello.
- Hello
- Goodbye
- Yes
Why are you talking again?
Did you get that many shots?
Here, intersection gas station
No, what is there?
Since I'm a card thief, I have it
There are no customers
Only flies fly away
What kind of coffee is this?
Why on earth are we ordering this much?
Whether you drink Namisa’s coffee again or not
What does it matter if I drink it with words?
Because he catches me so much!
Oh no, well, what happened?
Having a drink with a local friend
Because they pay attention to me
Yonghee too, Bungnam too
All of you except me
No, I'm not playing
Are they bullying you?
Why are you bullying me?
Ah, this is all you
That's because you act like a tiger.
Everyone was scared and watching
I married a tiger!
Where are you going? Come to work
Ugh!
oh!
Pasha!
Block the cross!
yes!
Special martial arts!
best
- Excellent, really.
- Really
Doyeonah
you are really so good
It's the best, really
- Just words?
- No.
Doyeon, come here
My uncle will give me pocket money.
Doyeon has pretty hands!
Hey, I have two pretty ones too, here
thank you
Doyeonah, Doyeonah
What does Doyeon like best?
Going to the amusement park with dad
But dad is always busy
Dad wants to go too
I can’t go because of this guy.
Doyeonah
To uncle Yo, ‘My dad.
Please give me a day off.' Okay.
- That's right.
- Please let me go to the amusement park with my dad.
Doyeonah
If you do that, you won't be able to use it.
My child's amusement park
I love it so much...
Don't feel pressured, team leader.
No, you have to bear the burden.
The kid wants to go
Don't feel pressured
yes
Deputy Director Choi, take a day off.
I went to the amusement park with Doyeon.
Just like that
You don't have to
Wow
Ah!
Honey is
First, go to the convenience store.
Beer...
Uh, okay
Fish oil, it’s refreshing
Wow, who went to the scene?
It looks like the vice minister's office is digging into it.
Why is that bastard so damned? Mr.
Still wondering who set it off?
yes
But the man who died first
You're a foreigner, right?
Looking at the internet
Well, what about a new day?
They say it smells like pseudo-religion.
At this point, it's just
Just hit it hard that way.
How about pushing it hard?
Hey, who can't do overwriting?
It's the easiest thing, that's it
But that thing
Because it keeps popping up only in Kiyun City right now.
Naeun-jae skewers...
Oh! Hey, hey, look at this, this, Mr.
Wow, this is Mr.
I'm talking about
How do I know...
How do you know...
AC
I am afraid that the IT special tourism zone will collapse.
Be scared, now
Ah, I was trying to make that.
I didn't even know this had happened, really...
Anyway you
Our stuff is gone
If you know what happened in Kiyun City,
We're all going to die
you come to your senses
yes
I can't connect...
Ah!
this human
Why aren't you answering the phone?
Please stop there in front
Ah, yes
Come on...
Are you here?
What does it mean to say ‘are you here’ to a customer?
Ah, well, you have to buy things to be a customer.
How much is it?
Okay, I got some change.
Let me ask you one thing
After graduating from high school
He only came to say hello during the election.
What's going on?
I'm so busy with construction projects.
Because I’m the president of the women’s association.
Do you have any news about the neighborhood?
Maybe an ATM?
when it exploded
Something like a video
I wonder if anyone took a picture
If there is
What trick are you going to do again?
What a masterpiece, wow...
What do you think of the members of the National Assembly of the Republic of Korea?
last time I
You saw the installation of intelligent CCTV.
It's all for the safety of this neighborhood
How do the local ladies react?
um
For posting it too late
They say they won't vote for you in the next election.
Eunjae
Do people not come around to you often?
- what?
- I'll give you this.
Just chew it
I'll chew it well
came, came
Here, here
It's too early now
- Boy, you have to go in.
- Oh, what's happening?
Thank you for coming despite your busy schedule.
Move often
Then I can eat Jesu’s food again.
How often do you move?
Come in quickly
- Please enter
-Chicken and Beer 2nd round
- Come in quickly.
- Please enter
- Go, quickly.
- Let's go
- I ate well.
- Go, quickly.
Have some chicken and beer
Oh, really
- Come quickly, come quickly.
- I'll have another drink.
Oh, I'm tired.
Who are you?
Are you awake?
both hands on the handle
Show the back of your hand
Okay, okay, ah, okay
I can't unlock the password for this
You waited
It's released
If you drop this from your hand, you will die.
It's not a joke
uh
close
Are you together?
Yes, but...
caught
The strongest?
Don't do anything useless
Receive what I sent
dashboard
Take the phone
Let the kid go
What about a new day?
Are you the one who stuttered?
Who are you?
How did you know about this place?
Why don't you answer?
The phone was disconnected...
What?
If this falls off the back of your hand
You said you were going to die, right?
You took it yourself.
Should I say I received this?
Should I say I stole it?
Unless this is a cannon phone
Looks like a secret phone
It's a secret phone.
How do you know?
I know it when I see it
Well done, JDD
Hey, but if it's a secret phone, this is it
Isn’t this what the military uses?
You know my name too
I know my house too
Hey, is it them? uh?
No, by blocking the satellite computer.
Are you trying to contact me through this?
Not the satellite computer side.
Looks like the other side...
The other side?
army?
I'm not sure
Director, are you doing well?
Boy, he was excited
I like money
"Reset scan
"Accessing log file"
Okay
Hey, the team members
I'm running around outside.
The team leader sits comfortably alone...
Are you going to fight?
How many hits do you want?
lonely and hard
You're working inside
Listen till the end
Why are you so angry?
Is it menopause?
I was a fool for replying
So
What, do you work one to two days with me? uh?
Why are you answering everything one by one?
Seohee Lee’s insurance payment was paid today.
Really?
Thank you, Ssal!
Madam, did you receive the insurance money well?
I'm glad it was organized well.
I, by any chance
Has the cost of the broken furniture been paid?
Ah...
No, it will be deposited.
yes
Take care of your meals, yes.
yes, yes
shoulder...
Ha, this guy really...
Oh, that, that bastard, really.
I'll take it, bro.
Uh, uh, yeah
Hello
Hey godfather
A person working in the financial sector
What if I miss the deposit date?
Did you bet on it?
Aren't you the guy who broke the table?
What is your name?
Is it your holy name?
This bastard is hungry
Just kill it, Mr.
My brother
Is this your friend?
Oh, is that your younger brother?
What kind of family business is this?
Tell my brother, the deposit date has passed.
Where are you now?
In your heart
Hello
You bastard
I just say what I have to say and hang up.
This is crazy
Ah, really, bastard.
Hey, you bastard.
Do you really want to get married?
Oh my, the person who wants to die
Where are you? uh?
And first you have to find me and kill me?
You brave bastard
Do you think I can't find it?
uh
Hello
Ha, bastard really, really
Why again?
Doyeon's father
Giyun Dream Kindergarten Choi Do-yeon father
Oh, or something
Hwang Mi-kyung, should I call you Seobu?
Where are you?
내가 사람 찾는 덴
선수야, 이 새끼야
너 지금 어디냐고
아이고, 겁나라
명함 뒤에 주소 있지
야, 이 미친 새끼야
그걸 알려 주면 어떡해
이 새끼야!
You really came, Mr.
Are you really here?
Let's not kill
What are you muttering to yourself?
Now, from now on
Answering one question at a time
One arm or one leg
Or
Break it as many times as the number of questions.
Hey, did you take your medicine?
one
How did you find out my family's name?
Your mom told me, why?
It's a trade secret.
two
in front of kindergarten
Have you ever visited?
If there is?
What are you talking about?
Just hit it
Block it, block it, Mr.
Let's not kill
IC
"Start data extraction
"Copying sectors"
Huh?
"Access granted
“Storage bypass successful”
Huh?
Done!
stop!
Please stop!
Stop, okay?
come out
I'm sorry
I was wrong, yes?
You ordered it, right?
I was wrong, I, I really
I'll live like I'm dead
I, I
I will never fuss again, I
Ding
That's not the answer
Anyway, I don't have the key so I can't open it...
What is it again?
Forensics completed
Everyone go to the store
no
iron
oh
- Hello
- Yes
hello
Again, again, again!
It's just me, it's just me, it's not there now
Guidance and even BlackBack videos
Everything has been restored
Hey, you worked hard.
Oh, I had a hard time
That piece of equipment also played a role.
Is it worth spending the money?
Hey, praise me too, okay?
You know this, I made it
It’s a handmade radio wave blocking tent.
Ah, this
We just need to block radio waves.
Even my life was almost cut off.
It's so hot
Hey, man, cost-effectiveness, cost-effectiveness, man
Oh, that's right, bro.
There is this
It costs about 30 million won to make it real.
But I'm there
I didn't even use 1/100th of it.
I admit it
Uh, thank you
I first checked the video
I'll upload it right away
Director, I asked you before.
Accident car black video
Ah!
Here it is
Huh?
Please speak comfortably, brother.
Is that so, Yonghee’s younger brother?
yes
Anyway, you had a hard time
You worked hard, you worked hard
Did you fight with this byeongnam?
It's not
Why am I fighting with a kid like that?
I won't fight
Yeah, we fought
Honey, you know, actually
I was with Minseo’s tutor earlier.
Magnifier Media PD Kim
Then until the strongest
Let's all gather together
They went into the hardware store, everyone together.
You can go too
Me, me?
I can't go, huh?
How do I get there?
I didn't get an invitation
How do I go?
I can't go
No, Chunbae brother too
After Myeongo Funeral Home
They said they didn’t see Byeongnam.
The sick man we knew is no longer there
changed
I'm alone
It's okay
I'll clean that up too, what can I say?
No, what kind of conspiracy are they plotting?
Thank you all for your hard work
Yonghee’s younger brother is amazing, really.
Sure, brother.
Huh? hello
Because of editing
Let's go first
First...
That's enough for me too, okay
Me too...
Hello mother
I need to wash up too.
I'll go, okay
Oh, me too
I have to go organize the stationery.
Byeongnam Kwak
Why? what?
What are these people planning to do while crowding around?
Have you been in?
I think it was more than 20 minutes.
Why doesn't it come out like this?
Whew
Our guy
It must be very difficult, right?
It's okay, I do that every day.
No, it's weird, huh?
in the neighborhood
It keeps exploding
At the same time, Choi Kang and I
Because I was there
Let's just get together and have it
What, huh?
How do I solve it, what?
That's what I was talking about, uh
Hey, you dishonest human being.
Only when I go out every night and drink alcohol
What about Ddongsampae?
In the neighborhood
There's such a strange thing
Do you just keep to yourself and keep quiet?
What a good thing
Are you talking about the neighbors?
Wow, who
Do you want to chat about the neighborhood? uh?
With Mr. Chunbae
You should have told me
We are the bank accountant and the president of the women’s association.
Hey, Brother Chunbae
I'm crazy because of my sister-in-law, huh?
And the mammoth, huh?
what?
Our innocent Kim Soo-il, huh?
You pretended to be busy
Except
I only play with Yonghee and Choi Kang.
My mouth came out a lot
You think that's it? uh?
Because of me
They say I won’t come even if I go to the supermarket.
It's not entirely wrong.
No!
If Soo-il finds out
Because they spread rumors around the neighborhood
Kim Soo-il likes people, right?
My mouth is heavier than yours
I don't care what we do together
Don't bully my husband
Got it?
They know what to do
Solve it? Mr.
Honey, team leader
They gave me leave to go to the amusement park.
Really?
Good
Choi Do-yeon will like it
But do I really have to go? uh?
If you look at the news, there are a lot of amusement ride accidents.
I'm afraid I'll fall into the bathtub
How do you order a bath?
Anyway, I'm being particularly mean to my daughter, huh?
Doyeon’s friends
He said he’s been to all the amusement parks.
Except Doyeon.
Still
There's no need to go now...
There is
He said he was on vacation
Don't say anything else, just go this time
- Turn off the lights
- Yes!
Video will be uploaded at midnight
Please like, comment, and subscribe
Magnifying Glass Media found it with great difficulty.
This is a vehicle black box video.
ATM machine
killed in explosion
On a foreign man's computer
With video of traffic accident at Giyun intersection
A suspicious map was found
What's scarier is
Seems like a terrorist attack
There was a warning message.
All three explosions were accidental
Contrary to the government's announcement
It may have been a planned explosion.
suspicious circumstances and
I found the evidence
Now, in the next video
Based on the evidence obtained by reporters
related to the bombing incident
Institutions, organizations, and people
I'll reveal it
thank you
Welcome
Welcome!
Places with as many people as possible
It would be better to avoid it
What do you say?
Don't sound like a grandpa
Have fun today
I want to go to the amusement park with my dad.
Singing every day
You're finally here
Huh? It's a rabbit
Dad, come quickly, come quickly!
Choi Do-yeon, don’t run, you’ll fall.
I won't fall
Doyeon looks like me
My motor skills are not normal.
Everything else has to resemble me.
Dad is coming to get you!
and!
eldest son, younger daughter
We get along well
I'm going too!
came
Doyeon!
Ugh!
One, two, three!
- Oh, thank you, thank you.
- thank you
Yes, this is the situation room.
Kiyun City
A warning of a bomb attack?
From what you said,
It is difficult to give a definite answer at the moment.
Attention everyone!
I put CCTV on my monitor.
Start searching for abnormalities
What should we do tomorrow?
um
Should we eat something delicious tomorrow?
Yeah
Team leader!
take a look here
What is it?
This way
You can see it.
Do you have tutoring today? Don't be late
Yeah, I'm going to catch the bus now.
Did you study in advance?
Lady, you’re nagging me, ah...
Who is it?
I should put it up
Minseo!
You can't come in here.
It's dangerous
- go back
- Get out of the way
- It's dangerous, go back.
- It's dangerous, go back!
- Get out of the way!
Instructor
Get out of the way, I'm in
no
The EOD team is coming now
What's going on?
she's my daughter
honey
Minseo!
mom
Minseo Kim
It'll be over soon
Do you trust mom?
yes
Now
It's okay
It's okay, take your time
Mom will see
Mom will take a look
mom
Minseo
Mom look look
There's enough time
Minseo, mom can do it
Okay?
are you okay
It's all over
Minseo did so well
Min, Minseo, dad is here
Our Minseo did a great job
You did so well
Well done, our Minseo
I'm going home now
this afternoon
suspected of being a bomb
There is a mysterious backpack
A report has been received
Police and military arrived immediately.
The bomb in question is
No real risk of explosion
It was a fake bomb
Confirmed
Conspiracy theories and all.
Because fake news is rampant, Mr.
Even the kids follow
Aren’t they all those damn people?
Hey, hey!
This bastard is about to die, Mr.
That's it
They're a subversive force, man!
Immediately arrest and investigate
What is it?
Hey, what are you guys!
Wait, wait...
Hey, don't mess with the server!
What, what are you guys?
What are you doing?
Ah, where are you going! uh?
What, what are you guys?
Oh, really! Mr.
i want to eat ice cream
You ate it earlier.
Just one more, okay?
If you eat a lot of cold food
I can't do it because my stomach hurts.
I don't have a stomachache
I also want to eat just one more
mom
Just one more
My stomach won’t hurt
They say my stomach doesn’t hurt
- Mom
mom, mom
Oh, I don't know
If Doyeon has an upset stomach, she takes responsibility.
Ah, if your stomach hurts, dad is responsible.
Yes!
Then I'll give you ice cream.
I'll go and get it
Yeah, I'm with Doyeon
I'll go to the bathroom and come back
- Yes, meet me in front of the bathroom.
- Yes
I taste strawberry
Okay, strawberry flavor.
Now
Doyeonah
Mom will go to the bathroom too.
Don't go anywhere, just wait
Yeah
Uh... can you please step aside for a moment?
Wow
Doyeonah
What is that ice cream?
I said my dad gave it to me
Who?
What kind of man...
No, no, no
It melts, eat it quickly
- Oh, good shot!
- Good shot!
- Is it bent? Where did you go?
- Yes, I went straight.
It's okay if you don't die
Hey
Yes, this is Seokjun Kim.
No, I...
If you think it's too complicated
There's no end to this
Yes?
No, the forces that overthrow the country
If you just sit there like this
What will happen to the country?
Is terrorism a separate thing?
Inciting the people
Spreading fake news
If this happens, it's terrorism.
Oh, by the way, that’s me!
Because I’m going to send it to a team that does a good job.
don't worry
Yes?
Yes, oh, really
Let’s eat sometime soon.
yes
Oh my, you frustrating bastard
Check this out, Mr.
Brother, let’s move.
uh
Oh, understand this.
When I talk about it...
Who is this?
yes
Minister Seokjun Kim
Yeah, who...
close
sullivan
James Sullivan?
The government
Control it with an embargo or
Really secretly
It could be moving.
Bombs in my neighborhood
Who are these people playing pranks?
707 Are you the youngest instructor?
Oh, what kind of neighborhood is all special forces?
What happened?
If the Minister is picky,
Because it can work out
Aw, just say it, Mr.
Now centered on Giyun City
something is happening
It must have been done meticulously on that side too.
Then we too
more precisely than that
Shouldn’t we do something?
Subtitle: Jang Se-ri